Guide to the WDBS Collection, 1949 - 1983
Duke University. University Archives
WDBS collection 1949-1983
WDBS (Radio station: Durham, N.C.)
8 linear feet Extent: 2130 Items
Duke University. University Archives
WDBS was Duke University's campus radio station from 1950-1983. It initially broadcast on AM by carrier current, a system in which radio signals were fed into the university's electrical system. In 1971, WDBS began broadcasting on FM 107.1 as a commercial, non-profit station. AM broadcasts ceased in the early 1970s. WDBS was sold in 1983 to repay debts the station owed Duke University. Collection includes annual reports, correspondence, proposals, newspaper clippings, advertising, program guides, record company photographs and press releases, and other materials related to the operation of WDBS. There are also reel-to-reel sound recordings of broadcasts from the 1960s and 1970s, including speeches by Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., Stokeley Carmichael, Douglas Knight, Samuel Dubois Cook, Charles Goodell, Robert Shelton, Spiro Agnew, Julian Bond, Birch Bayh, William Kunstler, Floyd McKissick, Richard Kleindienst, and Terry Sanford. News events and other subjects represented on tape include the 1968 Vigil, the 1969 takeover of the Allen Building by the Afro-American Society, racial unrest in Durham, anti-war activism, the 1971 USA Pan-Africa track meet, the 1972 Republican National Convention, the dedication of the William R. Perkins Library, and the Duke Symposium. Musical recordings include an organ recital, the Concert Band, and the Glee Club. English.
UA.31.12.0005
Language: English.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Use of audiotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies. Reference copies for a few of the tapes have been made on audiocassettes, and if a reference copy exists, it is noted in this finding aid. To arrange for the creation of reference copies of other items, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
Provenance
The WDBS Collection was received by the University Archives as transfers and gifts in 1969, 1972, 1974, 1979, 1981, 1996, accession numbers UA69-55, UA72-55, UA72-78, UA74-25, UA74-187, UA79-95, UA81-71, UA96-95.
Historical Note
WDBS was Duke University's campus radio station from 1950-1983. It initially broadcast on AM by carrier current, a system in which radio signals were fed into the university's electrical system. In 1971, WDBS began broadcasting on FM 107.1 as a commercial, non-profit station. AM broadcasts ceased in the early 1970s. WDBS was sold in 1983 to repay debts the station owed Duke University.
In 1947, three classmates from Rocky Mount, NC started a carrier current station called WCDC (for "We cover Duke campus".) They were persuaded to make their station an official university activity, and in 1950, WDBS began broadcasting from the basement of the Gray Building. In 1963, WDBS moved to the Bivins Building on East Campus.
In addition to music, the station presented campus news, national news, Duke athletics, and coverage of special events, including the 1968 Vigil after the death of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., the 1969 Allen Building takeover, and anti-Viet Nam War activities.
In 1971, WDBS purchased its FM license from Durham's WSRC. AM broadcasts continued for a time but ceased soon thereafter. Although owned by Duke, WDBS-FM operated independently as a commercial but non-profit entity. Initially run by students, by 1975 it was primarily staffed by professionals. The station was known for its extensive record collection, free form rock programming, and coverage of local events.
The purchase of the FM license, made possible by a long term loan from the university that was to be repaid from advertising revenue, put the station into debt from which it never recovered. Talk of selling the station's license, in order to pay back the debt to the university, began in the mid-to-late 70s.
In May 1978, WDBS agreed to sell its license to Village Broadcasting of Chapel Hill, pending approval from the Federal Communications Commission. Durham residents opposed to the sale petitioned the FCC to stop the license transfer. In October 1979, the Board of Directors of WDBS withdrew from the sale, citing the lack of approval from the FCC.
In 1980, the station moved from Bivins to Broad Street. In an attempt to increase listenership, WDBS changed its format from rock to classical during the day and jazz at night. In August 1982, WDBS agreed to sell to Classic Ventures, Ltd., pending approval by the FCC. The sale was approved in April 1983 and WDBS became an easy listening station. In 1984, it became WXFC.
There are some connections between WDBS and the later FM station, WXDU. In 1974, the unused AM carrier current system was revived as WDUR, playing Top-40, rock, and jazz. In 1977, WDUR became WDUK after a local commercial station petitioned the FCC for the call letters WDUR. In 1977, when the sale of WDBS was being considered, WDUK staffers proposed that students take over and operate WDBS. This proposal was eventually rejected. When WDBS moved off campus in 1980, WDUK moved into its former studios. In 1983, WDUK began broadcasting on FM as WXDU.
Collection Overview
Collection includes annual reports, correspondence, proposals, newspaper clippings, advertising, program guides, record company photographs and press releases, and other materials related to the operation of WDBS. There are also reel-to-reel sound recordings of broadcasts from the 1960s and 1970s, including speeches by Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., Stokeley Carmichael, Douglas Knight, Samuel Dubois Cook, Charles Goodell, Robert Shelton, Spiro Agnew, Julian Bond, Birch Bayh, William Kunstler, Floyd McKissick, Richard Kleindienst, and Terry Sanford. News events and other subjects represented on tape include the 1968 Vigil, the 1969 takeover of the Allen Building by the Afro-American Society, racial unrest in Durham, anti-war activism, the 1971 USA Pan-Africa track meet, the 1972 Republican National Convention, the dedication of the William R. Perkins Library, and the Duke Symposium. Musical recordings include an organ recital, the Concert Band, and the Glee Club.
Subject Headings
African Americans -- North Carolina -- Durham -- Political activity; African American student movements; Agnew, Spiro T., 1918-; Bayh, Birch, 1928-; Bond, Julian, 1940-; Carmichael, Stokely; Civil rights demonstrations -- North Carolina -- Durham; College radio stations; Cook, Samuel DuBois, 1927-; Duke University. Afro-American Society; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Duke University -- Students -- Political activity; Goodell, Charles E. (Charles Ellsworth), 1926-1987; King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1929-1968; Kleindienst, Richard G., 1923-; Knight, Douglas M., 1921-; Kunstler, William Moses, 1919-; McKissick, Floyd B. (Floyd Bixler), 1922-; Sanford, Terry, 1917-; Shelton, Robert M.; Student movements -- United States; Students -- Political activity; Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements -- United States; WDBS (Radio station: Durham, N.C.); Broadcasts; Sound recordings
Contents of Collection
- Annual Reports, 1951-1970
  Includes annual reports from the station manager, engineering manager, public relations manager, business manager, production manager, news editor, and other staff members. Also included are profit and loss statements, correspondence regarding equipment, equipment diagrams, program schedules, and other materials related to the operation of WDBS.
  - Annual reports, 1951-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1-15)
- Correspondence, Clippings, Histories, etc., [1949]-1983, undated
  - A Student Radio Station to Cover Duke Campus: Proposal, [1949] (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Charter, Bylaws, Operational Code, undated (Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1970-1983, undated (Folder 18)
    Most of the clippings concern events surrounding the proposed sale of the station in the 70s, a proposal by WDUK to assume the operations of WDBS and give control of the station back to students, community opposition to the sale, and the final sale of the station in 1983.
  - Correspondence, 1950-1970, undated (Folder 19)
    Memos and correspondence, including a 1950 plan for installing a campus radio station and a 1966 report on the feasibility of a campus FM station.
  - Financial: Budgets, Advertising Brochures, etc., 1960-1968, undated (Folder 20)
  - History of Radio Station WDBS, Part I, 1947-1957. J. Robert Brubaker, 1958 (Folder 21)
  - History of Radio Station WDBS, Part II, 1958-1968. J. William Veatch, III, 1968 (Folder 22)
  - News Wire Reports, circa 1967-1968 (Folder 23)
    Printed teletype reports from United Press International (UPI). Most of the news stories pertain to 1968 presidential primaries.
  - Miscellany, 1954-[1978], undated (Folder 24)
    Bumper stickers, promotional items, and other materials.
  - WDBS-FM: Loan Request Proposal with Exhibits and Related Data, copy 1, 1970 July 11 (Folder 25)
  - WDBS-FM: Loan Request Proposal with Exhibits and Related Data, copy 2, 1970 July 11 (Folder 26)
  - Radio Council, 1965-1971, undated (Folder 27)
  - Radio Council Petitions for Positions, circa 1962-1970 (Folder 28)
  - Wiring Diagrams, undated (Folder 29)
  - WDBS 107.1 FM Stereo, circa 1974, UA96-95, poster (Opaperfolder MC20)
  - Your Radio Station, 1971, UA81-71, 12 inch phonograph record, one-sided (Audio-disc D1)
- Program Guides, 1973-1980
  The WDBS Program Guide began as a weekly pamphlet that listed the week's programming. By 1974, it published monthly, accepted advertising, and featured articles, fiction, poetry, photography, and a calendar of local cultural events.
  - Program guides, 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 30-35)
- Record Company Promotional Materials, circa 1970-1980
  Photographs, posters, press releases, and other materials supplied to WDBS by record companies.
  - Promotional materials (Box 4)
- Audiotapes, 1956-1973, undated
  All recordings are on 1/4 inch tape on 7-inch reels unless otherwise noted. Tapes are arranged chronologically. The original labelling on the tape boxes is transcribed here, even though in some cases it may seem anachronistic or insensitive (i.e., the term "Afros" used as an abbreviation for "African-Americans.")
  - Interviews, addresses, and other news coverage, 1960-1973, undated
    - Post-Christian Man Symposium (8 reels), 1960 Nov. 15-1960 Nov. 17 (Box 5)
    - Glenn Negley: Last Lecture, 1961 Mar. 9
    - Martin Luther King, Jr.: Page Auditorium 1964 Nov. 13
      - Reference Copy: Sound Cassette. UA79-95-20.
      - Another recording of Dr. King's speech is in the collection: Radio TV Services Records. Reels B-224-A and B-224-B.
    - Symposium on the South in Continuity and Change: Allan Sindler, 1965 Feb. 22
    - Symposium on the South in Continuity and Change: Joseph J. Spengler, 1965 Feb. 22
    - Rosa Weinstein Lectures: Dr. Martin Fox, 1966 Feb. 16-1966 Feb. 17
    - Symposium: Newcomen Society, 1966 Apr. 14, (10 inch reel) (Box 8)
    - Stokeley Carmichael: Interview, 1967 Mar. (Box 5)
      - Reference Copy: Sound Cassette. UA79-95-21.
    - Stokeley Carmichael: Page Auditorium 1967 Mar.
      - Reference Copy: Sound Cassette. UA79-95-22/23/24
      - Another recording of Carmichael's speech is in the collection: Radio TV Services Records. Reels B-608-A and B-608-B.
    - Middle East Crisis, 1968 Mar. 8-1968 Mar. 9, (10 inch reel) (Box 8)
  - WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, 1968 Apr. 5-1968 Apr. 10
    Cassette listening copies and reel-to-reel dubs of the following tapes in the WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil series are in the University Archives' Duke Vigil Collection. In May, 1968, WDBS dubbed its collection of reel-to-reel tapes of the Vigil and donated the dubs to the Rare Book Room (later transferred to University Archives). Cassette listening copies were made from these dubs. Some of the originals of these tapes are missing from the WDBS collection and presumably exist only as dubs in the Duke Vigil Collection; however, there are some discrepancies between the numbering of the tapes in the two collections, making it difficult to determine if all the tapes in the WDBS collection are represented in the Vigil collection.
    - Vigil #1, 1968 Apr. 5 (Box 5)
      Pete Seeger Spots by Paul Robert Conroy; In the Beginning: Friday night, April 5, 1968, Speech in the Alumni Lounge by Dr. John Strange to the group just before marching to Dr. Knight's home.
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 1. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-1
      Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 1. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-1/2
    - Vigil #2, 1968 Apr. 5
      Dr. Knight at home-talks with Jack Boger and Jon Kinney, commentary by Ken Ross, Dave Birkhead, Paul Robert Conroy. Ken Ross with 20 minute actuality on Dr. Knight talking to the vigil at his home, questioned by Jack Boger, et al.
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 2. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-2.
      Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 1. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-1/2.
    - Vigil #3, 1968 Apr.
      Missing.
      The original of this tape is missing from this collection. It presumably survives as WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 3. Apr. 5-8, 1968, in the dubbed tapes in the Duke Vigil Collection. The description of the tape from that collection reads:
      Pres. Knight at home Friday night, answering questions from the group concerning non-academic employees, their wages, and his membership in the Hope Valley Country Club. Press conference, Monday, 12:30pm in the Varsity 'D' room: John Strange, Bunny Small, John Kinney.
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 3. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-3.
      Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 2. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-3/4
    - Vigil #4, 1968 Apr.
      John Strange (Alumni Lounge) as on tape no. 1
      Statements by: Dean William Griffith
      Dr. James Graham
      Tupp Blackwell for the S.S.O.C.
      Mr. Ted Minah
      University spokesman (Bindewald)
      Dave Birkhead
      Chris Jossi
      The original tape no. 4 from the WDBS collection described above does not correspond to any of the dubbed tapes in the Duke Vigil collection. Tape no. 4 in the Duke Vigil collection is labeled:
      WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 4, April 8, 1968-April 10, 1968 Press conference, continued: John Strange, Bunny Small, John Kinney. Dr. Martin Luther King's "I have a dream" speech played several times to the assembled vigil on the quad. Wednesday, April 10, 1968, main quad: John Strange and Wright Tisdale addresses, singing of "We shall overcome."
      This tape from the Duke Vigil Collection does not seem to directly correspond to any of the tapes in the WDBS Collection.
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 4. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-4.
      Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 2. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-3/4.
    - Vigil #5, 1968 Apr. 6
      At Dr. Knight's House, April 6, Sat. p.m.
      a. Huck Gutman-on Local 77 Strike
      b. Questions on the 4 demands
      c. WDBS Actualities (most same as #4)
      Mr. Ted Minah-statement on strike
      Mr. Bindewald-same
      Mr. Ted Minah-appeal for student workers
      d. Jack Boger-on what to do now
      e. Dr. John Strange-same
      f. Law student, Dave Hunt
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 5. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-5.
      >Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 3. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-5/6.
    - Vigil #6, 1968 Apr.
      The original of this tape is missing from this collection. It presumably survives as Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 6, April 6, 1968-April 7, 1968, in the dubbed tapes in the Duke Vigil Collection. The description of the tape from that collection reads:
      Dave Hunt, John Kinney, Jack Boger, Peter Brandon for Local 77, Paul Conroy, interview with Chris Dulaney, John Strange "move to the quad." Sunday: Bunny Small on the quad, Bill Veatch interviews with Marc Kaplan, Peter Brandon, Griffith.
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 6. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-6.
      Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 3. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-5/6.
    - Vigil #7, 1968 Apr. 7
      Sunday, April 7, 1968, on the main quad:
      Dr. John Strange, reading from Dr. King
      Bunny Small recaps the past 43 hours
      Jon Kinney
      general announcements
      comments on the Black students
      Huck Gutman, reading Thoreau
      Algerian grad student
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 7. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-7.
      Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 4. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-7/8.
    - Vigil #8, 1968 Apr. 7
      Sunday, April 7, 1968, cont. rally on the main quad:
      Singing led by Nick Atkins, organizer for Local 77, et al.
      Announcements by Lucy Brady, Food Committee Chairman
      Tape of Dr. Martin Luther King's "I have a dream" speech, Washington, 1963
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 8. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-8.
    - Vigil #9, 1968 Apr.
      The original of this tape is missing from this collection. It presumably survives as tape no. 10 of the dubbed tapes in the Duke Vigil Collection. Tape no. 10 of the WDBS Collection (labeled rally on the main quad., cont.) corresponds to tape no. 11 in the Duke Vigil Collection (also labeled rally on the main quad, continued), so it is assumed that the missing tape no. 9 in the WDBS Collection corresponds to tape no. 10 in the Duke Vigil Collection (labeled rally on the main quad). Tape no. 9 in the Duke Vigil Collection corresponds to tape no. 11 in the WDBS Collection.
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 10. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-10.
      Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 5. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-9/10.
    - Vigil #10, 1968 Apr. 8
      Rally on the Main Quad, cont.
      Questions and answers from the assembled Duke Vigil to and from:
      Mr. Ira Sanford
      Miss Joan Baez
      Mr. David Harris
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 11. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-11.
      Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 6. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-11/12.
    - Vigil #11, 1968 Apr. 10
      a. Address by Dr. Samuel Dubois Cook to the assembled Vigil, Wednesday. April 10, 1968, time, ten minutes.
      b. Statement to the students of Duke University, read to the assembled Duke Vigil, by Wright Tisdale, Chairman of the Board of Trustees, Wednesday, April 10, 1968, Time: five minutes.
      Dub: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Tapes of the Duke Vigil, no. 9. 1 sound tape reel (1200 ft.): 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. UA68-347-9.
      Address by Samuel Dubois Cook is also on Reference Copy: Duke Vigil Collection: WDBS Cassette 7. 1 sound cassette. UA68-347-10.
    - Vigil #12, 1968 Apr. 10
      Speeches on the Main Quad
      1. Dr. John Strange
      2. Mr. Wright Tisdale, Chairman, Duke University Board of Trustees (same as 11)
      3. Dr. John Strange (remarks on #2)
      4. Replay of speech by Dr. Samuel D. Cook to the assembled Vigil by WDBS (same as 11)
    - Vigil: Baez, 1968 Apr.
      1. Ira Santel? [Sanford]
      2. Joan Baez
      3. David Harris
      at the Duke Vigil on the Main Quad
  - Allen Building Takeover, 1969 Feb. 10-1969 Mar. 12
    Cassette listening copies for the WDBS Allen Building Takeover series are in the University Archives' Allen Building Takeover Collection.
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #1, 1969 Feb. 13 (Box 5)
      Cassette listening copies this and the following tapes in the WDBS Allen Building Takeover series are in the University Archives' Allen Building Takeover Collection.
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #1. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-1/2.
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #2, 1969 Feb. 13
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #3, 1969 Feb.
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #2. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-3.
    - Page Meeting, part 1: Tape #4, 1969 Feb. 13
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #3. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-4/5.
    - Page Meeting, part 2: Tape #5, 1969 Feb. 13
    - Dick Gregory Visit, Allen Building Takeover: Tape #6, 1969 Feb. 10, 1969 Feb. 17
      1. Afro Allen Bldg Takeover wrap-up report; Chris Santy-correspondent Feb. 17, 1969
      2. Report by Chris Santy (David Christy) on visit of Dick Gregory to Duke campus Feb. 10, 1969
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #4. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-6.
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #7, 1969 Feb. 13-1969 Feb. 16
      Afro Take Over of Allen Bldg. Reports by Chris Santy (alias David Christy)
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #5. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-7/8.
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #8, 1969 Feb. 15
      Rally at Dr. Knight's house after Afro-Am takeover of Allen Building. Recorded by Duke Univ. Information Services
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #9, 1969 Feb. 15, 1970 Jan. 21
      1. Actualities for Page Convocation, 12:30 p.m., Feb. 15, 1969
      2. Tom Fine spot hospital workers sit-in. Statement by Doctor who allegedly struck black hospital worker, Jan. 21, 1970
      3. Robert Chapman spot on sit-in by workers affiliated with Local 1199D at Duke hospital arrested for trespassing after nursing office sit-in, Jan. 1970
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #6. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-9.
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #10, 1969 Feb. 15
      Part I: Convocation-Introduction of president of Afro-Ams at Page. Recorded following Afro take-over of Allen Building.
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #7. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-10/11.
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #11, 1969 Feb. 15
      Part III: Convocation called by students following Afro take-over of Allen Bldg.
      Contents:
      Howard Fuller (part II)
      Tom Rainey of History Dept.
      Dean Griffith (part I)
    - Convocation at Page following Allen Bldg. takeover: Tape #12, 1969 Feb. 15
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #8. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-12.
    - Convocation at Page Auditorium, part 2: Tape #13, 1969 Feb. 15
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #9. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-13/14.
    - WDBS News: Tape #14, 1969 Feb.-1969 Mar. (Box 6)
      1. Preface by Dr. Knight aired Feb. 15, 1969 7pm
      2. Don Baumgardner, Mar. 10, 1969
      3. Apollo 9 liftoff by ABC radio
      4. President Knight resignation, Mar. 27, 1969, Baumgardner and Braswell
      5. President Knight at his home during the Feb. 1969 crisis
    - Dr. Knight's Speech: Tape #15, 1969 Feb. 16
      Reference Copy: Allen Building Takeover Collection: WDBS Allen Building Takeover Tape #10. 1 sound cassette. UA79-95-15.